It's a beautiful day
Hold me close
I'll be dead in my eyes
Dead in my eyes
Till the day that I die
Dead inside
I just wanna feel alive
With you I'm alive
Fell in love but it left me lonely
Tried to trust but it burned me slowly
I didn't know what I was looking for
Till I found her
I found her
Without her
I'm a mess
There was nothing about that love that made sense
I was stressed
Till I found her
Found me lonely
Lost and lonely
One step away from this
Getting it up slowly
I was a mess
I was afraid
I'd be the girl who just put up a wall
So no one could break
Till I found him
Running through the world without a heart
Made me a whole one out of the parts
Suddenly it's like I'm here
Didn't know that love was real
Until I caught hold
Too close
I'll be dead in my eyes
Dead in my eyes
Till the day that I die
Dead inside
I just wanna feel alive
With you I'm alive
Fell in love but it left me lonely
Tried to trust but it burned me slowly
I didn't know what I was looking for
Till I found her
I found her
Without her
I'm a mess
There was nothing about that love that made sense
I was stressed
I found her
Without her
I'm a mess
There was nothing about that love that made sense
I was stressed
I found her
Till I found her
Ooo